Mr. President, if I could ask you, you
said that there's a deal, an agreement
in place. Are you willing to lower
tariffs on steel and aluminum?
>> Well, we're looking at that.
>> But in order to get farmers to get
tariffs lowered
>> Well, we're getting zero for our
farmers. You know, farmers have been
hurt very badly by Canada. And they
won't be paying any tariffs anymore. And
uh we may bring uh some of the tariffs
down to a level where other countries
are cuz Canada was paying a higher
tariff. Canada was paying us a higher
tariff. So, we are Look, we have a a
very nice relationship with leadership
right now. And we'll see, but we did a
3-day pause. It was supposed to be a 50%
straight across the board tariff that
was going into effect at 7:00 this
morning. And I delayed it at the request
of Canada for 3 days so we can iron out
the details. Uh but it it's going to be
a a wonderful deal, hopefully a
wonderful deal for everybody. Uh
>> Mr. President, earlier today you said
North Korea has something like 57
nuclear weapons. They've been expanding
their nuclear program. Is your goal in
re- trying to re-engage with Chairman
Kim still denuclearization? And And what
makes you think you could be successful
now when you weren't
>> Well, I don't want to talk about that,
but I do have a good relationship with
Kim Jong-un.
Uh as you know, you've seen. Uh
He didn't like Biden. He didn't like
Obama. He didn't like anybody, but he
likes me and I like I you know, I just
got along with him very good. We had We
had great meetings. We speak. Uh and I
think uh our nation and I think other
nations, frankly, whether it's Japan or
or South Korea, they're a lot safer if
I'm president than somebody else is pre-
president. Now, I didn't like the fact
that we're doing these massive military
exercises really against North Korea. It
was a you know, a exercise against North
Korea when I'm friendly with him, when
we have I don't see anything happening
for
certainly 2 and 1/2 years. It's not
going to happen with me. But uh I don't
see anything happening and I was not
happy when South Korea said, "No,
they're not interested in helping us
with the Hormuz Strait." And yet they
get 60% of the royal from the Hormuz
Strait. I said, "Would you like to help
us?" He said, "No, thank you." I said,
"That's nice. Please, thank you." He
made us a lot of money. I didn't like
that. So,
uh I I felt that to do a massive We were
doing a massive war exercise,
I thought that was very insulting to
somebody that frankly has been
during my term, at least, uh very
well-behaved.